99firms.com 2019-10-29

# Privacy and Cookie Policy - 99firms.com

This Privacy and Cookies Policy describes how 99firms.com (hereafter known as “website,” “us” or “we”) collects, uses, and protects information. This Privacy Policy pertains to any collected personal information, received data, as well as reporting.

## Privacy Policy

### What Information We Collect

The extent of personal information does not extend past your name and email address. The collected data will not be taken without explicit consent from you, our visitor.

We also collect your IP address to obtain and implement cookies. This is a standard procedure used on many sites on the web, and it’s done to improve your user experience, as well as for data about how the site is used. Please, refer to our Cookie Policy below for more information.

Finally, we collect data such as website visits. This information is meant for our internal use only and does not, and will not, contain any personal information.

### How We Use the Information

All use of collected information must be presented to the visitor before it is collected. Promotional emails and material are only sent to visitors should they choose to subscribe to the said service. Any cookies and personal information collected is used strictly to improve the user experience and present relevant content to the visitor. Finally, any information collected is used toward resolving any complaints you might have with us.

### Who Do We Share the Information With

We do not share, sell or rent any personal and non-personal information with anyone, unless:

  * The government or a relevant government agency make an official request
  * We need to protect our rights and property
  * If there are indications of fraudulent and harmful behavior coming from you that the government and relevant government agencies should be aware of

### Security

We assure our visitors that all information held by us is safeguarded and all appropriate implementations are in place to protect said information from cyber-attacks and theft, as well as illegal usage and distribution of previously mentioned information, as appropriated by the US law.

### External Links

Our website uses external links. Due to entirely voluntary nature of customers to follow said links, as well as the fact that we do not control the content these links point to, we are not eligible for any harm or loss occurring from following these links.

## Cookie Policy

“Cookies” are digital pieces of information stored on your hard drive by a web server. Cookies cannot, and will not, run any programs nor contain malicious software of any kind, and is used solely to personalize the user experience off whom they’re collected. However, you may disable any cookies at your leisure, though this might reflect negatively on your user experience.

### Disabling Cookies

Cookies can be disabled in your browser. Here are the links explaining how cookies are disabled on each of the most prominent web browsers.

### Changes to Policies

99firms.com reserves the right to revise and change all policies herein presented to accommodate changing business policies and legal requirements. However, 99firms.com will duly notify the visitors of the changing policies on the website.

If you use our site, it automatically means you agree with our Privacy Policy. If you disagree with our Privacy Policy, we must ask you to stop using our services forthwith.
